Class of 1955 Records, 1951-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1955 Records
1951-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1955.
RG 80 UUID:874de971-2ba4-43aa-b5bc-763ef9933d09
4 boxes (1.15 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1955.
The Class of 1955 was the seventy-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1955 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1955, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1955 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Clipping 1977 (Box 2199, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Music 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Photographs 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 4)
- Commencement-Speaker 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1951-1952 (Box 2199, Folder 6)
- Groups 1951-1955, 1978 (Box 2199, Folder 7)
- History 1977 (Box 2199, Folder 8)
- Hoop Rolling 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 9)
- Illumination Night 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 12)
- Junior Ushers 1954 (Box 2199, Folder 13)
- Class Letters 1966-2004 (Box 2199, Folder 14)
- Officers 1952-1955 (Box 2199, Folder 15)
- Organization 1951-1955 (Box 2199, Folder 16)
- Reunions undated (Box 2199, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 2199, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 2199, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 2199, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 2199, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1980 (Box 2199, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1995-2000 (Box 2199, Folder 23)
- Reunions 2005 (Box 2199, Folder 24)
- Senior Prom 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 25)
- Sophomore Carnival 1953 (Box 2199, Folder 26)
- Class Supper 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 27)
- Who's Who 1951 (Box 2199, Folder 28)